path2usa.com 2010-06-25

# Privacy statement - Path2usa

**COLLECTION AND TRACKING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

So that we can provide you with the most efficient and enhanced service, we may request information about you. We may also collect personally identifiable information such as name, email addresses and demographic information. We also may collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring Web site address. 

There are links to third party sites on our website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information users consent to give to third parties not affiliated with Path2USA. Any information users give to another party is governed by the rules of that party’s privacy policy, which may differ from this Privacy Policy. Path2USA is not responsible for information given to other parties. 

**WHAT WE DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION**

We may use personal information in order to display custom, personalized content to our visitors and send newsletters, emails, features, promotional material, surveys and other updates to our users. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our service, respond to any problems that may arise and to gauge user trends to determine what part of our services are most popular with users.

We may extend offers to users on behalf of our partners about a particular product or service that may be of interest to you, but we will never give out your name or personal information at any time without your permission. 

We allow users of our Web site to send articles or links by email to other parties who may be interested in them. We do not retain any email to other parties who may be interested in them. We do not retain any email addresses (unless you are a user who already has voluntarily provided your email address) of either the sender or receipt of such articles or links after they are sent. 

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request (e.g., subpoenas); to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation. 

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information online (whether through Path2USA’s services or any other services available online), personal or otherwise, that information could be collected and used by others. For example, if you use chat forums, bulletin boards, and you post your e-mail or id, you may receive unsolicited messages form others. Path2USA has no control over this use of your personal information.

**USE OF COOKIES**

Your browser offers so-called “cookies” which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a Web site. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. Cookies simply assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. Cookies will also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our Web sites are viewable even if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features of our site, as well as other Web sites, will not be available to you.

Some of the banner ads displayed in our Web sites are provided by outside companies. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web sites, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information. 

**USE OF WEB BEACONS**

Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons, which are also called single-pixel gifs. These images allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We also may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. Some of our Web pages may also contain Web beacons placed there by our advertising partners to help us determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns. 

**CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

A user may, at any time, change, correct, modify or delete any personal information they may have provided to Path2USA by contacting Path2USA service. 

Finally:

The Web is an evolving medium. If required, we may change our privacy policy at any time in the future, without any notice to the users. However, the changes will be posted here. Use of any information will always comply to our privacy policy, even if we later change this policy.

You also must read our **Terms and conditons** prior to use this website.
